bootstrapcheatsheets.com 2017-07-27

# Privacy Policy — Bootstrap Cheat Sheets

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the  _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  website at _bootstrapcheatsheets.com_. This site is operated by James Croft, trading under the business name [Go Make](http://gomake.com.au/).

 _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Crh), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.

## Collection of your personal information

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, when purchasing a product at  _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  you may be required to submit personally identifiable information.

## Sharing of your personal information

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service.  _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

## Use of your personal information

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

 _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

## Accessing Your Personal Information

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know.

## Contacting us

 _Bootstrap Cheat Sheets_  welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us at [contact@bootstrapcheatsheets.com](mailto://contact@bootstrapcheatsheets.com) or simply fill out the form below.
